Prince Yu,
I unintentionally
overheard a few words between you and Prince Shuo just now.
I am dull-witted.
I hope Your Highness can enlighten me.
The matter Miss Tang is asking about
will, after all, damage my sixth brother's reputation.
As his older brother...
Prince Yu.
Since Miss Tang trusts me,
I won't be afraid of him blaming me
and will just tell the truth.
Your Highness means
that woman
looks like me,
but was...
There are many people in Sixth Brother's mansion.
You just need to ask around
to know I'm telling the truth.
Miss Tang.
Greetings, Miss Tang.
This way.
Okay.
Miss Tang is back.
Miss Tang.
Take my advice.
My sixth brother has suffered since childhood,
so he tends to go to extremes.
Even if you want to save your own life,
you must never disobey him.
Your Highness means that
if I cannot obediently
stay in Prince Shuo's Mansion,
my life will be in danger.
Learn from the mistakes
of those before you.
Never mind.
I can't help but admire
Miss Tang's excellent pipa playing.
If you ever need anything,
just send me a message.
I will meet your requests.
After all, I am his brother,
so I can always put in a good word for you.
Thank you, Your Highness.
It seems Prince Yu was telling the truth.
I need to plan ahead.
What's wrong?
Let's go. Stop looking.
The dignified Prince Shuo
is entangled with a mere musician.
Aren't you afraid of being laughed at if word gets out?
It's not what you think.
Let me explain.
Seeing is believing.
Tang Zhiluo.
Why can you be pleasant to everyone else
but refuse to listen to me?
I am the one you should trust the most.
Aren't I?
You've said enough, Your Highness.
May I say a few words?
These past few days, you've locked me in your mansion,
and I'm being watched everywhere.
I know you are deeply in love with that Miss Tang,
but she is gone forever.
Although I look somewhat like her,
we are not the same person.
Why force it?
You don't just look like her.
You are her.
I am not.
Prince Shuo.
Tang Zhiluo is just a lowly musician.
Even though my status is low,
I will never let anyone trample on me.
Tang Zhiluo.
I'll say it one more time.
You are the one I'm looking for.
You're awake.
I'm sorry.
I failed to consider your feelings.
This is...
On your arm,
do you have an identical mark?
I can't believe there's such a coincidence in this world.
This is too unbelievable.
Let me think about it.
You're hurt.
I'm fine.
Then I'll go get a doctor.
It's fine.
As long as you don't leave,
anything is fine.
Are you satisfied with my medical skills, Your Highness?
Very satisfied.
Could predestined love from a past life be real?
No.
Even if it's a predestined marriage...
But I have to stay alive first.
Prince Shuo is unpredictable.
It's too dangerous to stay here.
But how can I escape?
Fake my death to escape.
Prince Yu.